ORGANIZATIONAL STRATEGY

Trusted analyst and consultant with proven success collaborating with internal stakeholders at all levels to design and implement initiatives that improve decision making and organizational effectiveness. Use statistical and data visualization approaches to align strategies and tactics with business climate, historical data, and requirements. Lead engaged teams focused on successful completion of deliverables throughout complex, high-visibility projects. Maintain executive presence, mindfulness, and sense of humor, cultivating cohesive work groups and positive morale. Areas of expertise:

Workforce Analytics | R | Julia | C++ | Java

Team Leadership | Research | Technical Consultation | Writing & Editing | Program Evaluation | Budget Forecasting Global Project Management | Business Case Development | Modeling | Financial Reporting | Personnel Development Coaching & Mentoring | Executive Presentations | MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ACCENTURE PLC, CGU TALENT INNOVATION LAB, Claremont, CA: Consultant | 03/2019 - 05/2020

Global HR / Recruitment Transformation Research & Development Lab

Managed project deliverable content and translated research into business cases. High-impact examples provided below.

<u>Project</u>: Future workplace job redesign research and market analysis for account executive role

Role: Project Lead | 11/2019 - Present

- Directed final project deliverables for new client, CEO's strategic advisor.
- Formulated, pitched, and executed strategy project that provided technical recommendations for assessing, developing, and predicting future developmental trends related to high-impact role of account executive. Presented results to senior leadership. Project continues in new phase with estimated completion in May 2020.
- Pitched product offering predicted to increase scope of work 50%–200% for talent innovation lab during fiscal year to provide evidence-based and research-driven organizational development approach. Generated new ideas based on insights gleaned from recent acquisitions with similar roles.
- Led project team (consultant, project manager, 2 assistants); managed performance and career development.
 - Trained team on client onboarding, acculturation, pitching and public speaking, time management, technical mentoring, and cross-functional communication. Served as resource for strategy insights and revenue ideas.
 - Onboarded new team members while delivering short-term, high-impact project; created culture of fast, direct, and thorough feedback to expedite integration into team.
- Collaborated with principal consultant to create scope of work; managed budget and created timeline. Performed business intelligence (BI)/analytics, reviewed literature, created and recommended role assessment tools.

<u>Project</u>: Documentation sprint to prepare final presentation of vetted global employee selection and assessment model <u>Role</u>: Project Manager \mid 10/2019 - 12/2019

- Managed project timelines, milestones, personnel time, and task budgeting, overseeing 5 team members.
- Performed archival research and drafted internal marketing documentation.
- Presented deliverable to senior leadership, completion 30% ahead of schedule and 40% under personnel budget.

ACCENTURE PLC, CGU TALENT INNOVATION LAB, Claremont, CA: Associate | 11/2018 - 03/2019

Consulted with stakeholder managers on organizational behavior, management, statistics, research methods, interviewing, and focus groups during 4 projects. Created interviewing/hiring criteria as member of Recruitment and Selection Committee.

Project: Validation of scoring measure for behavioral interview into secondary implementation with global alignment teams

Project: Development of values-based assessment prototype

Project: Selection assessment design prototype

Project: Leadership model synthesis and design

Role: SME, Consultant, and/or Focus Group Interviewer

- Directed deliverable content, translated research into business case for internal clients, and oversaw adherence to project requirements. Completed all projects within deadlines and budgets.
- Reviewed literature to develop behavioral interview theory. Initiated implementation plan with global management.
- Served on Strategy Committee for each project. Advocated for project budgeting needs and formulated primary strategy for using past projects to pitch to new internal stakeholders.

ARUP, Los Angeles, CA: Management Consultant | 09/2019 - 12/2019

Participated in organizational effectiveness evaluation plan as consultation team member for North America regional HR.

- Persuaded local office to evaluate onboarding program and implement needed changes throughout the Americas region. Partnered with 5 team members to create company's first-ever developmental and formative evaluation plan for new hire onboarding program across IT, HR, facilities, and finance departments. Maintained team strategy/focus.
- Designed logic model that described inputs, outputs, and short-/long-term outcomes of program aligned with values of company's founder. Wrote and edited white paper deliverable.
- Developed and presented program enhancement and monitoring recommendations to senior HR managers to improve employee engagement, reduce turnover, promote communication across departments, and increase productivity. Recommendations adopted by executive team and implemented throughout region.

LISA KACZMARCZYK PHD CONSULTING, LLC, Claremont, CA: Statistical Consultant | 09/2019 - 02/2019

Initiated and created customized analysis tool based on social network theory, yielding high level of client satisfaction during intermediate program phase, with final program results and academic publication status pending.

- Designed bespoke social network analysis tool used by client to narrate theory of change for large, complex client
 organization consisting of consortium of large universities instituting inter-disciplinary STEM program nationwide.
- Analyzed social network of cross-section of 3 attitudinal constructs across 3 university systems, including actor-event network graphs, interpretation consultation, and commented Rmarkdown script.

GETTY LEADERSHIP INSTITUTE, LEAD LABS, Claremont, CA: Executive Coach | 05/2019 - 08/2019

Guided 3 senior international museum executives through intensive assessment center process during leadership training.

- Assisted clients in creating development plans based on assessment center, 360°, and StrengthsFinder results; promoted post-program accountability for reaching goals by following up 6-8 weeks after program completion.
- Coached executives toward improved decision making and suitable roles for their individual skillsets.
- Led ad hoc team check-in sessions, cultivating positive mindset and high morale during assessment center.

UNDISCLOSED PROPERTY MANAGEMENT FIRM, Los Angeles, CA: Management Consultant | 03/2019 - 06/2019

Participated in organizational culture project for private, family-owned property management firm undergoing succession-related change with \$1B+ portfolio of real-estate assets. Led overall strategy for culture assessment and acted as go-to for executive presentations. Managed confidential information by creating and upholding non-disclosure agreement.

- Diagnosed internal-facing stress related to values signaling from family management through executive management.
- Provided strengths-based assessments that offered corrective advice.
- Connected business strategy with identified cultural values for implementation in management training program.
- Developed business case for implementing value communication strategies to grow organizational performance.
- Delivered final pitch of organizational culture assessment to senior executive team to provide guidance with business strategy alignment while gauging current climate for internal corporate and operational roles.

BOSTON CONSULTING GROUP GAMMA DATATHON, Los Angeles, CA: Team Lead | 03/2019 - 04/2019

Built and led cross-functional team of 5 experts in artificial intelligence, financial engineering, data science, management, and organizational behavior for invitation-only case competition for data analytics group of graduate students.

- Provided case formulation training, common strategy language, and high-level architecture for technical solution.
- Led group meetings and created synergies as go-to technical translator to simplify engineering language.

ICM PARTNERS, Century City, CA: Management Consultant | 09/2018 - 01/2019

Contributed to organizational behavior project for Top 5 creative talent agency undergoing HR restructuring.

- Collaborated with consulting team to design 1-year training framework and employee development plan that aligned evidence-based organizational development to business performance related to training costs for specified roles.
 - Converted variable costs to fixed costs projected to reduce training expenses \$10K-\$15K per new hire.
 - Presented plan to CHRO and organization, resulting in partial implementation at pilot stage.
- Led team in overall strategy, coached team members, and resolved conflicts.

Prior experience as university lecturer, clinician, network operations engineer and IT consultant, 2007 – 2018

EDUCATION

CLAREMONT GRADUATE UNIVERSITY, Claremont, CA: Master of Arts (MA) in Organizational Behavior & Evaluation | 2020 SOFIA UNIVERSITY, Palo Alto, CA: Master of Arts (MA) in Clinical Psychology | 2013 NAROPA UNIVERSITY, Boulder, CO: Bachelor of Arts (BA) in Traditional Eastern Arts | 2010